ACTWU's Organizing Department Records. 5619/007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- National Spinning Co., 1966 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- National Spinning Co., 1966-1967 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  Whiteville, NC
- Natona Mills, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  Dallas, PA
- Nova Mills, Inc and Camillo Mills (Textile), 1980 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  Farmingdale, NJ
- Ohio City Mfg., 1978 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Oneita Mills, 1971-1975 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  Andrews Lane, South Carolina and Cullman, Alabama
- Opelika Mfg., 1980-1983 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  Hawkinsville, GA
- Opelika Mills, 1970-1977 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  Alabama
- Park Silk, 1973-1979 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Phillips Fibers, 1966-1979 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  Rocky Mount, N.C.
- Phillips Fibres, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  Rocky Mt, NC
- Phoenix Glove Co., 1981 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  Andrews, SC
- Pioneer Co., 1982 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  Div. of National Home Products
- Plus Mark, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  Division of American Greeting Cards
- Porritts and Spencer, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  Wilson, NC
- Prowler Industries, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  Lindsay, Ont.
- RSN Corp., 1979 (Box 50, Folder 20)
- Rexind ( Rexham) Corp (Office Unit), 1978 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  Edinburg, Indiana
- Robertson Factories, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  Bairdsford, PA
- Romac Container, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  Cleveland, Ohio
- Rona Plastics, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 24)
- Ross Laboratories (Abbott), 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  Alta Vista, Va.
- Will Ross Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  Subsid: White Knight, Ozark, Alabama and Fulton Instrument, Fulton NY
- Saunders Mfg. Co., 1973 (Box 50, Folder 28)
- Schlelel Mfg. Co., 1975 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  Maryville, Tenn.
- Schwab Safe Company, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 30)
- Scott Laboratories, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 31)
- Southampton Textile Company, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  Emporia, VA
- Sovelco Mills, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  Winston Salem, NC
- Sponge, INC, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 34)
- Standard Keil, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 35)
- Stearns and Foster, 1976-1976 (Box 50, Folder 36)
- StyleMaster, Inc., 1981 (Box 50, Folder 37)
- Syntex Corp, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 38)
  Petersburg, VA
- Tennford Weaving, 1978-1980 (Box 50, Folder 39)
  Stanford, Maine
- Textile Paper Products Co., 1964-1968 (Box 50, Folder 40)
  Hendersonville, NC
- TEXFI Industries, Inc, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 41)
- Texprint, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 42)
  Macon,GA
- Thermo Plastics, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 43)
  Whittaker Corp. Pineville, SC
- Time Corp., 1969-1975 (Box 50, Folder 44)
- Tiogo Weaving, 1972-1974 (Box 50, Folder 45)
- Toledo Optical Laboratory, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 46)
  Toledo, Ohio
- Transam Warehouse of Illinois, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 47)
  Forest Park South
- True Temper Plant, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 48)
- True Temper Corp., 1969-1970 (Box 50, Folder 49)
- True Temper Campaign, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 50)
- United Merchants and Manufacturers, 1967-1982 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- U. S. Hat Board, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  Annison, Alabama
- U. S. Padding Corp., 1977 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Victor Electric Wire and Cable Corp., 1979 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  Westerly, Rhode Island
- Victor Electric, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  Westerly, R.I.
- Waveline, Inc, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  Fairfield, NJ
- Waynesboro Knitting Co., 1970 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Webster Brick, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  Somerset, VA
- Wellman Campaign, 1971-1976 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Fred Whitaker Co. ,Inc, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  Roanoke, VA.
- Wonder Knit (Div of Rapid American), 1980 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  Galax, VA
- J. Wood Co., 1979-1980 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  Milroy, PA
- Woonsocket Spinning Co., 1980-1981 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Woonsocket Spinning Co., 1978-1980 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Quebec, Canada, 1980-1982 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Far West, 1979-1982 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Canada. TWUA History, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Los Angeles Counties Organizing Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- West Coast. L. A. Organizing Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- West Coast Organizing Committee, 1974-1978 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- New England General, 1980-1981 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Connecticut, 1977-1981 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Maine, 1976-1983 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Southern New England, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- New Hampshire, 1976-1980 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Massachusetts, 1980-1981 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Greater Fall River, 1976-1981 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Rhode Island, 1976-1981 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- ACTWU Rutgers and Hanes Corp, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Canada General, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- N. E. Reg. Conf (Texas Division), 1982 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  Ramada Inn- Boston Mass
- New England Regional Conference, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  Ramada Inn. Boston, Mass
- New England Staff Meeting, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  Providence, R.I. March 2nd
- North East Coordinated Org. Comm. Mtg, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  Providence, R.I. February 2nd
- New England Staff Meeting, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  Providence, R.I. October 25th
- New England Staff Conference, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  Providence, R.I. December 7th
- New England DeLegnie Conference, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  March 20-21st
- New England Org Joint Board, 1979-1980 (Box 52, Folder 21)
- Mid West, 1980-1982 (Box 52, Folder 22)
- Meeting- Chicago Joint Board, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  January 29th
- Haggar, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Hallmark Cards, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  Smithfield, R.I.
- Hanes Corp., 1982 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Hanes Corp, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Hanes Report. Project Planning Book, 1981-1982 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Hanes Corp (subs. Consolidated Foods), 1979-1981 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Hanes Knitting, 1966-1980 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Hanson Industries, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Harris Corp, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  Rochester,NY
- Harold and Jack Kahn O. D.,Inc, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Hartford Fibers, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  Kingston, Ont.
- Health-TEX (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Hellenbrand Industries, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Harriet and Henderson. Cotton Mills, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  Henderson, N.C.
- Hermann - Herzman of Penn, 1978-1980 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Hexcel, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Hill Industries, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  Hillsboro, Texas
- Joseph B. Hoffman Inc, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  Richard Textile Division
- Home Curtain, 1976-1977 (Box 53, Folder 19)
- Hodgson, Thomas and Sons, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  Suncook, NH
- Hoover Universal, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 21)
- Hope Webbing, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 22)
- Hoover University, Inc, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  Franklin, KY
- Bernard Pincus (Box 53, Folder 24)
- Huyck Felt, 1977-1979 (Box 53, Folder 25)
- Hybrid Systems Corp., 1981 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  Keene, NH
- Idlewild Farms, 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  Pomfret Center. Conn
- Ideal Tapes, Lowell, Mass, 1977-1980 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  Chelsea Industries
- Imperial Fabrics and Décor, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 29)
- Independent Unions in New England (Box 53, Folder 30)
- Indian Head Mills, 1969-1976 (Box 53, Folder 31)
- Interstate Uniform, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  Service Corp. Nashua, NH
- Int. Packaging Co., 1981 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  Bristol, NH
- Int. Plastics Co., 1977 (Box 53, Folder 34)
- Irvin Industries, Inc., 1979 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  Blytheville, Ark. and Greenwood, Miss
- IVACO, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 36)
- Janesville Products, 1977-1979 (Box 53, Folder 37)
- Jantzen, Inc, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 38)
- Kahn and Feldman, Inc, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  Subs. of Jefferson Mills. Pulaski, VA
- Jet-Pak Corporation, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 40)
- Jobst Institute, Inc, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 41)
- Johns-Manville Corp, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 42)
- Jomac, Inc, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 43)
- Kandy Textiles (Beavertown Mills) (Box 53, Folder 44)
  Scottsboro, Alabama
- Karen Textile (Box 53, Folder 45)
  Occum,Conn
- Katz Underwear Co., 1980 (Box 53, Folder 46)
  Honesdale, Pa
- Kellwood, Inc, 1979-1982 (Box 53, Folder 47)
- Kendall Co., 1972 (Box 53, Folder 48)
  Athens, GA
- Kendall Co., 1980-1981 (Box 53, Folder 49)
  Griswoldville, MA and Walpole, MA
- Kendall Mills, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 50)
  Augusta, GA
- Kendall- Various Plants, 1973-1981 (Box 53, Folder 51)
- Kendall Co. (Subs. Colgate-Palmolive, Inc.), 1969-1976 (Box 53, Folder 52)
  Franklin,KY
- Kennametal, Inc, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 53)
- Kenyon Piece Dye Works, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 54)
- Keystone Weaving Co., 1977 (Box 53, Folder 55)
- Walter Kidde and Co., 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 56)
- Kimberly Clark, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 57)
  Henderson, NC
- Kingston Mills, 1976-1977 (Box 53, Folder 58)
  Kingston, NY
- Kiwi Polish Co., 1980 (Box 53, Folder 59)
  Pottstown, PA
- Knox Woolen, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 60)
- Kobacker Stores, Inc., 1980 (Box 53, Folder 61)
- Kolmar Mfg. Co., 1976 (Box 53, Folder 62)
  Milwaukee, Wisc
- Kordite Plant, 1965-1966 (Box 53, Folder 63)
  Macedon, NJ
- Kraemer Textiles, Inc, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 64)
  Nazareth, PA
- Lace Auxiliary Workers', 1981 (Box 53, Folder 65)
  Beneficial Association
- Laich Industries, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 66)
- Lakeview Country Club, Inc, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 67)
  subs of Penn Machine Co. Inc. Morganstown, West Virginia
- Lawrence Hose, 1975-1976 (Box 53, Folder 68)
  Haw River, Inc
- Lee Damor, Inc (Box 53, Folder 69)
  Feasterville, PA
- Lehigh Valley, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 70)
- Levi, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 71)
  Corpus Christi, Texas
- Lifetime Foam Products, Inc, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 72)
  (subs. Sears, Roebuck) Conyers, GA
- Limited Stores, Inc, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 73)
- Limited Stores, Inc, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 74)
- Litchfield Fabrics, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 75)
- Litton Industries, 1978-1980 (Box 53, Folder 76)
- M. Lowenstein and Co., 1970-1982 (Box 53, Folder 77)
- Ludlow Corp., 1978 (Box 53, Folder 78)
  Indianola, Miss
- Ludlow Jute Co., 1977 (Box 53, Folder 79)
  Ludlow, Mass
- Lydall Corp., 1979-1980 (Box 53, Folder 80)
  Div of Western Acadia
- Lyman Printing and Finishing Co., Inc, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 81)
  Lyman, SC
- Mt. Vernon Mills (Box 53, Folder 82)
- Mtd. Products Inc., 1980 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Magic Pan, Inc (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Malden Mills, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  North Berwick, ME
- Malina Company, 1979-1982 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Manette Mills, Inc, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Maremont Corp., 1979 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Mark One, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Martin Corp, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  Bridgeton, NJ
- Martin, J. B. Company, 1966-1967 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  Leeville, SC
- Maryland Cup Corp., 1979 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  October 25th
- C. H. Masland, 1981-1982 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Mastex Industries, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  Holyoke, Mass
- Medalist Industries, Inc, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Meiwa USA Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Megas (Box 54, Folder 15)
  Brooklyn Heights & Cleveland Ohio
- Metro Pants (Box 54, Folder 16)
  Harrisburg, VA
- Microfibers, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  Pawtuckett, R.I.
- Mid-America Yarn Mills, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  Div of Clinton Mills. Yuma, Arizona
- Midwest Handbag, 1976-1977 (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Milco Industries, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 20)
- Miller and Sons, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  Hazelton, Pennsylvania
- Miller's Brewery, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  Eden, NC
- Modern Carpet Industries, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  Poteau, Oklahoma
- Modern Filter, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  West Haverstran, NY
- Mohasco Corp, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 25)
- Mohawk Bedding, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 26)
- Mohican Mills, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  Lincoln, NC
- Monsanto [folder 1 of 2], 1970-1971 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  Pensacola, Florida and Decantur, Alabama
- Monsanto [folder 2 of 2], 1968-1979 (Box 54, Folder 29)
- Montgomery Mills, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  Montgomery, PA & Union S.C.
- George C. Moore., Inc, 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  Greenville, Tenn
- George C. Moore, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 32)
- Moran Mills, 1979-1981 (Box 54, Folder 33)
- Moran Mills, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 34)
  Fayetteville, NC
- Munsin Packaging, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 35)
- Munsingerwear, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 36)
  Fairmont, NC
- Munsingerwear, Inc. Plants, 1967-1978 (Box 54, Folder 37)
- Munsingerwear, Inc. Plants, 1978-1981 (Box 54, Folder 38)
- J. & J. Plant Info Contract (Box 54, Folder 39)
- J. & J. Wage & Benefits Summaries (Box 54, Folder 40)
- J. & J. Wage and Benefits Summaries (Box 54, Folder 41)
  Originals
- J. & J. Miscellaneous, 1982-1983 (Box 54, Folder 42)
- J. & J. Newsletter, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 43)
- J. & J. News clippings and Materials, 1980-1983 (Box 54, Folder 44)
- J. & J. Plant Lists, 1979-1982 (Box 54, Folder 45)
- J. & J. Leaflets and Campaign Material (Box 54, Folder 46)
- J. & J. Fact Sheets, 1980-1982 (Box 54, Folder 47)
- UAW. Region 5, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 48)
- United Labor Relations Board. Arbrook Inc., 1978 (Box 54, Folder 49)
- Arbrook Inc, 1978-1980 (Box 54, Folder 50)
- Arbrook Inc, 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 51)
- J. & J. Wage Increases, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 52)
- J. & J. Summary of Wage Increases, 1980-1982 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- [There is no folder 2] (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Medtech Plastics, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  S. Plainfeld, NJ
- N. J. Ethylene Oxide, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Johnson and Johnson, 1981-1982 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Johnson and Johnson Contracts, 1981-1983 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Annual Reports, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- J. & J. Productivity & Quality Circles, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Chayes-Virginia, Inc, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- J. & J. Contract Language Proposal, 1979-1982 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Albuquerque Workers, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- J. & J. Plants- Puerto Rico, 1975-1982 (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Dervo Plant, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  J & J. Lubbock Texas
- Johnson and Johnson, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  El Paso, Texas
- Ethicon, J. & J., 1982 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  San Angelo, Texas
- Johnson and Johnson, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  Arlington, Texas
- J. & J. Critikon Project, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 17)
- J. & J. Texas Plants, 1979-1981 (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Albuquerque, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 19)
- J. & J. Dentist Products Campaign, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 20)
- J. & J. Plants listed by Region, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 21)
- J. & J. Eticon, Albuquerque, 1980-1982 (Box 55, Folder 22)
- J. & J. Fact Sheets, 1979-1982 (Box 55, Folder 23)
- J. & J. Plants, 1980-1982 (Box 55, Folder 24)
- J. & J. Contracts, 1979-1983 (Box 55, Folder 25)
- Johnson and Johnson " To Do Items", 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 26)
- Johnson and Johnson, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 27)
- J. & J. Montreal, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 28)
- J. & J. Southington, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 29)
- J. & J. Incentive Task Force, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 30)
- Johnson and Johnson Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  October 20th
- J. & J. Meeting Staff, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  Feb. 8th
- J. & J. Conference, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Johnson and Johnson Meeting, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  NYC. January 12th
- Chicago Johnson and Johnson Conference, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  February 6-7th
- J. & J. Organizing Meeting, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- J. & J. Delegate Conference, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  Edison, NJ. May 13-14th
- Ethicon, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- J. & J. Plants, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  Southern Region
- J. & J. Stimtech Plant, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  Minneapolis, Minn
- J. & J. Plants- Mid West Region, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Johnson and Johnson Correspondence with Regional Directors & Legal Dept, 1980-1981 (Box 56, Folder 12)
- J. & J. (American Catherers), 1981 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  Indian Mills, NJ
- J. & J. (American Catherers), 1981 (Box 56, Folder 14)
- J. & J. Corporate Heights & Parking Deck Campaign, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  New Brunswick, N.J.
- J. & J. Plants. Quin State, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 16)
- J. & J., 1981 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  Ortho Distributing Whse. Elyria, Ohio
- Johnson and Johnson, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  Vascore Division. Anaheim, California
- Johnson and Johnson, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  New Bedford
- Johnson and Johnson, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 20)
- Johnson and Johnson, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  Dental Products Division. East Windsor, New Jersey
- Johnson and Johnson Southington, 1979-1981 (Box 56, Folder 22)
- Jelco Lab. Johnson and Johnson, 1980-1981 (Box 56, Folder 23)
- Jelco Lab ( J. & J.), 1980 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  Southington, Connecticut
- Savoy Leather Mfg. Organizing Info about Targets, 1982-1983 (Box 56, Folder 25)
- Staff Retirement, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 26)
- Misc. Documents, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 27)
- Eastern Missouri Food and Beverage Trades Council, 1982-1983 (Box 56, Folder 28)
- Seles Knitting. Tultex Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 56, Folder 29)
- ACTWU., 1978-1983 (Box 56, Folder 30)
- Appeal by Helen Hriczak, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 31)
- Appeal by Julia Brazel and Misc., 1983 (Box 56, Folder 32)
- Report on Company and Union Activity, 1982-1983 (Box 56, Folder 33)
- Staff Assignments and Changes, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 34)
- Companies Under ACTWU Contract with Both Apparel and Textile Units, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 35)
- Branch Plants and Tex Apparel Org. Plants (Box 56, Folder 36)
- Southwest Coordinated Organizing Program, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 37)
- Automatic Data Processing, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 38)
  Clifton, NJ
- Current Organizing Campaigns, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 39)
- Issue Research, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 40)
- National Production Workers Union, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 41)
- Juston Industries, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 42)
- Juston Boot Co., 1981 (Box 56, Folder 43)
- ACWU- fights for fairness in freeze, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- South, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- J. P. Stevens, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Upper South, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Mid West, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Canada, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Quin, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- New England, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- New York, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Levi Strauss and Company. Misc., 1975-1982 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- ACTWU Staff. Weekly Organizing Activity Report, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Health Care [folder 1 of 2], 1971 (Box 57, Folder 12)
- Health Care [folder 2 of 2], 1970 (Box 57, Folder 13)
- Congressional Record, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 14)
- Memos to General Officers, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 15)
- Staff Lists, 1979-1982 (Box 57, Folder 16)
- Worker to Worker. Ideas for Articles, 1978-1980 (Box 57, Folder 17)
- See Sheinkman, 1976-1983 (Box 57, Folder 18)
- International Trade and the Burke-Hartke Bill. Speaker's Handbook (Box 57, Folder 19)
- Unorganized Sports Equipment Companies, 1978-1980 (Box 57, Folder 20)
- Rally- Re: J. P. Stevens, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  Indianapolis, Ind. October 1st
- J. P. Stevens (Box 58, Folder 2)
  Religious
- J. P. Stevens- Rates of Pay, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- JPS - Research on Company, 1969-1975 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- J. P. Stevens- A. Philip Randolph Institute, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- J. P. Stevens: Brendeon Sexton, 1977-1980 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- J. P. Stevens- Staff Vacancies, 1977-1978 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- J. P. Stevens: Howard Samuel, 1977-1978 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- J. P. Stevens: Shareholders Actions, 1976-1977 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- J. P. Stevens: Stock Ownership, 1976-1977 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- J. P. Stevens Staff, 1976-1979 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- J. P. Stevens: Staff, 1976-1980 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- J. P. Stevens: Staff Meeting, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  November 15-16th. Holiday Inn. Chicago
- J. P. Stevens: Social Justice, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 14)
- ACTWU Information Kit for Press, Television, and Radio, 1976-1978 (Box 58, Folder 15)
- Recidivist Report, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Stockholders Mtg., 1977-1978 (Box 58, Folder 17)
- J. P. Stevens Report on Human Rights and Stockholders Mtg, 1977-1978 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  Thunderbird Motel
- J. P. Stevens Workers Rally, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  Spartanburg, S.C. November 20th. Photographs Included
- J. P. Stevens Staff Conference, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  Atlanta, GA. September 11-12th
- J. P. Stevens: Straightening Things Out, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 21)
- J. P. Stevens: Roanoke Rapids Community Status of Officers, 1977-1980 (Box 58, Folder 22)
- J. P. Stevens Rally, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  Aug. 24th
- Speakers and Guests, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 24)
- Rally for JPS Workers, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  City Auditorium. Spartanburg, SC. November 20th
- Charters, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 26)
- ACTWU and General Officers & Leadership, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 27)
- JPS- Rally Spartanburg, 1977-1978 (Box 58, Folder 28)
- J. P. Stevens: Social Justice, 1976-1980 (Box 58, Folder 30)
- J. P. Stevens- Sales Outlets: Institutions, 1974-1976 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- J. P. Stevens, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  Sales Outlets: Direct Sales
- J. P. Stevens- Shuttle, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- J. P. Stevens: Spotlights, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- J. P. Stevens: Dan Shriver, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- J. P. Stevens: Speakers Bureau, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Stevens: Stockholders Meetings (Annual), 1975 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- J. P. Stevens: Supervisors, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Szold, Brandwen, Meyers and Altman, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- J. P. Stevens- Testimony before Thompson Committee, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- J. P. Stevens: T.A.R.I.F.F. and Gorga, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- J. P. Stevens: Harriet Teller Requests Referred to her, 1976-1978 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- J. P. Stevens: Trade Shows and Other Events, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- J. P. Stevens: UAW, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 14)
- J. P. Stevens- Unfriendly Letters, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 15)
- J. P. Stevens- Tax Scandal, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- J. P. Stevens- TWUA News Releases, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- J. P. Stevens: T. V. Networks, 1976-1977 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- J. P. Stevens: Wage Rates and Benefits ( Work Folder), 1976 (Box 59, Folder 19)
- J. P. Stevens Wages and Benefits in some JPS Plants, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 20)
- J. P. Stevens, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 21)
- J. P. Stevens- Harry Wittschen, 1975-1976 (Box 59, Folder 22)
- J. P. Stevens: Worker to Worker Program, 1978-1979 (Box 59, Folder 23)
- J. P. Stevens Stockholders' Mtg, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  Greenville, SC. March 7th
- J. P. Stevens: Textile Labor, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 25)
- The Stevens Worker, 1976-1979 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  Formerly Stevens Organizer
- J. P. Stevens: Weekly Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 59, Folder 27)
- J. P. Stevens: Young People Socialist League, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 28)
- Committee Assignments (Box 59, Folder 29)
- J. P. Stevens: N. A. Zonarich, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 29)
- The Organizer (Box 59, Folder 30)
  Vol.1 No.1
- Southern Wage Drive, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Local 169, Kilmer Caban (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Louis Simon ( Amalgamated. Services and Allied Industries Joint Board), 1977-1980 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- William Himer: ACTWU, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Upper South Organizing, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Upper South, 1980-1982 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Southern Wage Agitation Drive, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Canvass Reports- Quin State, 1980-1981 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Greater New York Joint Board, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  Local 1790
- New York State, 1980-1981 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Deep South, 1980-1982 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Quin State and New York State, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Vice Presidents and Regional Directors, 1977-1980 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Pennsylvania Organizing Projects, 1977 (Box 60, Folder 14)
- J. Courey; R. Harris; T. Hummel, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 15)
- ACTWU: Charles English, 1977-1981 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  Southern Director
- ACTWU Weekly Organizing Activity, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  M. Robillard; P. R. Downing; H. Mickel; C. Sheerer; F. M. Walls; S. Young
- Weekly Organizing Activity Report, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  Mid West. D. Bruneau; J. Barry; D. Krenik; D. Rathke; W. J. Smith
- Weekly Organizing Report, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  J. Barry; H. Mickel; J. Miller; E. Nichols; J. Orange; R. Rose; R. Ross; C.L. Sutton; C. Sheerer; E. M. Walls; A. York
- Weekly Organizing Report, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 20)